drsquatch.com 2019-12-02

# Website Terms and Conditions of Use

###  1\. Terms 

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law. 

###  2\. Use License 

  1. Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Dr. Squatch's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not: 
    1. modify or copy the materials;
    2. use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
    3. attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Dr. Squatch's web site;
    4. remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
    5. transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.
  2. This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Dr. Squatch at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format. 

###  3\. Disclaimer 

The materials on Dr. Squatch's web site are provided "as is". Dr. Squatch makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Dr. Squatch does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site. 

###  4\. Limitations 

In no event shall Dr. Squatch or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Dr. Squatch's Internet site, even if Dr. Squatch or a Dr. Squatch authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you. 

###  5\. Revisions and Errata 

The materials appearing on Dr. Squatch's web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Dr. Squatch does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Dr. Squatch may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Dr. Squatch does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials. 

###  6\. Links 

Dr. Squatch has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Dr. Squatch of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user's own risk. 

###  7\. Site Terms of Use Modifications 

Dr. Squatch may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use. 

###  8\. Governing Law 

Any claim relating to Dr. Squatch's web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of Nevada without regard to its conflict of law provisions. 

General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site. 

###  Privacy Policy 

This Privacy Policy applies to our information gathering and dissemination practices for drsquatch.com (the “Site”), which is owned by Dr. Squatch, Inc. (“Dr. Squatch”, “we”, “our”, or “us”). Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting the personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) that you disclose to us. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand the type of information we may collect from users (“User” or “you”) who visit our Site, how we use the Personal Information and non-personally identifiable information that we collect, and how we protect your Personal Information. By using the Site, you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. This Privacy Policy is written in the English language. We do not guarantee the accuracy of any translated versions of this Privacy Policy. To the extent any translated versions of this Privacy Policy conflict with the English language version, the English language version of this Privacy Policy shall control. 

###  1\. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION 

Dr. Squatch collects information that enables us to operate the services we provide to you. In connection with certain aspects of the Site, we may request and collect certain Personal Information to obtain our products or use our services. Personal Information may be collected when you register or submit information on the Site. Non-personally identifiable information, that is about you but individually does not identify you, may be collected, including but not limited to: Site usage, IP address, referral URL, the used browser, as well as operating system. Here are some examples of the type of information we collect and how we may use it: 

###  2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE 

When you create an account on the Site, make purchases with us, join a subscription program, share product reviews, and/or sign up to receive offers or email, we collect the information that you provide to us such as (1) your name, email address, street address, city, state, zip code; (2) the user name and password that you use to register an account on the Site; (3) financial information for payment processing purposes; and (4) comments, reviews, suggestions and/or other such information that you may provide. You acknowledge that this information may be personal to you, and by creating an account on the Site and providing Personal Information to us, you allow us to identify you. We may use your contact information to send you information about our services in connection with your use of the Site. You may unsubscribe from receiving such messages at any time by contacting Dr. Squatch or through your account settings on the Site. 

###  3\. INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY 

Our Site automatically collects some information from your web browser when you interact with the Site, including your IP address or other unique identifier for the computer, mobile device, tablet or other device you use to access Site, including the mobile network information. This information is used to facilitate collection of data concerning Users’ interaction with the Site, such as the number and frequency of visitors to the Site, which helps us analyze and make improvements to the Site by making it more responsive to the needs and preferences of Users. This information does not identify you personally. 

###  4\. COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES 

We may use cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, mobile analytics software, log files, or other technologies to collect certain information about your online activity, and interactions with our emails, online and mobile advertisements, and to allow us to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables Dr. Squatch to improve our services and provide you with more relevant content and advertising offered by Dr. Squatch, or through or linked from our services. You may, however, disallow receiving cookies at any time through your web browser. It is not our intention to use cookies to retrieve information that is unrelated to our Site or your interaction with our Site. 

###  5\. FINANCIAL INFORMATION 

We use third party processors to collect payment information (such as a valid credit card number, type, expiration date or other financial information) to process payments for customer transactions. This information is required to be submitted as part of our checkout process. We do not have access to any of this financial information it is submitted directly to our third party payment processing company (the “Payment Processor”), which uses it to process your payment. The use and storage of that information is governed by the Payment Processor’s applicable terms of service and privacy policy. 

###  6\. THIRD PARTY USE OF INFORMATION 

We will not disclose your Personal Information to third parties for any purpose without your consent unless for the following limited purposes: 

###### Third Parties Providing Services on Our Behalf:

We may share information with third party service providers, such as the Payment Processor, who perform services and functions on our behalf to support our interactions with you. These third party service providers may assist with technical operation of our Site, provide analytics, process orders, transactions and payments, or provide customer service. We may also share non-identifying information, such as aggregate statistics or usage information, with third parties.

###### Your Consent To Have Your Personal Information Shared:

In connection with your use of the Site, you may be asked to opt-in to receive informational or marketing offers, or to otherwise consent to the sharing of your information with a third party, including social networking sites such as Facebook Instagram, or Twitter. If you agree to have your Personal Information shared with a third party, your Personal Information will be disclosed to the third party and will be subject to the privacy policy and business practices of that third party.

###### Legal Disclosure:

We may transfer and disclose information, including your Personal Information, usage information and device identifier, (including IP address), to third parties to comply with a legal obligation; when we believe in good faith that the law requires it; at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation; to verify or enforce our agreements, terms of use or other applicable policies; to respond to an emergency; or otherwise to protect the rights, property, safety, or security of third parties, visitors to our Site or the public.

###  7\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY 

Dr. Squatch will never knowingly request or collect personal information from any person under 18 years of age without prior verifiable parental consent. If you are under 18 years old please do not provide your information on our website. 

###  8\. SPECIAL NOTE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS 

California law entitles residents to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties or with corporate affiliates for those entities direct marketing purposes. Dr. Squatch does not provide any personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. If you want to request a notice or have any questions about Dr. Squatch privacy practices, please contact us. In addition, if you are a California resident under the age of 18 and are a registered user, you may request us to remove content or information posted on our websites or stored on our servers by (a) submitting a request in writing to support@drsquatch.com and (b) clearly identifying the content or information you wish to have removed and providing sufficient information to allow us to locate the content or information to be removed. However, please note that we are not required to erase or otherwise eliminate content or information if (i) other state or federal laws require us or a third party to maintain the content or information; (ii) the content or information was posted, stored, or republished by another user; (iii) the content or information is anonymized so that the minor cannot be individually identified; (iv) the minor does not follow the instructions posted in this Policy on how to request removal of such content or information; and (v) the minor has received compensation or other consideration for providing the content. Further, nothing in this provision shall be construed to limit the authority of a law enforcement agency to obtain such content or information. 

###  9\. LINKS TO THIRD PARTY WEBSITES 

The Site may contain links to other sites as a convenient method of accessing information that may be useful or of interest to you. This Privacy Policy and the practices that we follow under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the websites of any third party. We are not responsible for the content, accuracy, or opinions expressed on any third party website or for the privacy practices or security standards used by third parties on their respective websites. You understand and agree that by clicking on a link to a third party’s website, you have left our Site and the Privacy Policy stated on the Site is no longer in effect. 

###  10\. USER CONTENT 

Some features of the Site may now or in the future allow you to provide content, such as written comments or reviews, or interactive content such as quizzes, to be published or displayed on public areas of the Site (“User Content”). All content submitted by you to the Site may be retained by us indefinitely, even after you terminate your account. By submitting any User Content, you grant to Dr. Squatch a perpetual, worldwide, irrevocable non-exclusive, royalty-free license to use the User Content in any manner, including to create derivative works, without any compensation or notice to you. Your User Content may be posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. We cannot control the actions of other Users of the Site with whom you may choose to share your User Content. 

###  11\. RIGHT TO OPT OUT 

When you register with us, or if you provide additional Personal Information through our Site, we provide you with the right to “opt out” of receiving future communications from us for direct marketing purposes by indicating that you decline such communications. You may choose to have your name taken off of our email list after you have registered or provided additional information by emailing us at support@drsquatch.com. 

###  12\. SECURITY OF YOUR INFORMATION 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure against loss, unauthorized use, disclosure or destruction and when transferring information for processing. However, due to the open communication nature of the Internet, no electronic data transmission or storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us. 

###  13\. CONSENT TO PROCESSING & INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS 

Dr. Squatch is a global business and may process, transfer and store information about our Users on servers located in a number of countries, including the United States. As a result, your personal information may be subject to data protection and other laws that may differ from your country of residence. Your Personal Information may be disclosed in response to inquiries or requests from government authorities or to respond to judicial process in the countries in which we operate. By using the Site, or by providing us with any information, you consent to the collection, processing, maintenance and transfer of such information in and to the United States and other applicable territories in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as, or equivalent to, those in the country where you reside and are a citizen. 

###  14\. DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS 

At this time, we do not respond to browser "do not track" or "DNT" signals. 

###  15\. CHANGES TO THE PRIVACY POLICY 

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the Services or sending you an email. A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Services after such changes have been first posted.
